We are here in a quiet demonstration to demand from our government to do everything they can
to release the Israeli hostages that are held alive right now in Gaza Strip.
We tell our government a very clear message.
Don't talk to us about flattening Gaza, about bringing it back to the Stone Age.
Don't promise us more death and more casualties and more blood.
We want you to work on the living.
We want you to promise us that you will do everything you can to come to a deal to release the hostages.
Do everything you can to save the lives of people that are still alive.
What you do right now as a government is disappoint us and to abandon us once again.
We are abandoned enough.
We are heartbroken.
We need a true and a real responsible power in the leadership to promise us that we can survive this moment.
The entire people that live here, please come to a deal.
Release the hostages now.